insidefutbol.com 2017-12-23

# Football - Privacy Policy | Inside Futbol | Latest Football News, Transfer Rumours & Articles

**PRIVACY POLICY OF  **

**WWW.INSIDEFUTBOL.COM**

_**Definitions**_

In this privacy policy references to “we”, “us” and “our” are to [www.insidefutbol.com](http://www.insidefutbol.com/)

References to “our Website” or “the Website” are to [www.insidefutbol.com](http://www.insidefutbol.com/)

References to “the Business” means Inside Futbol Limited

‘cookies’ are parcels of text sent by a server to web client (browser) and then sent back unchanged by the client each time it accesses that server. Cookies are simple pieces of data unable to perform any operation by themselves – they are neither spyware nor viruses. Cookies are used for authenticating, session tracking and maintaining specific information about users such as site preferences or the contents of ‘shopping carts’.

**1\. Type of Information We Collect**

When you use the Website the information we collect via the Website may include:

Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.

Your preferences and use of email updates (if any).

Your IP address. This is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website.

Data recorded by the Website, which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings. This saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on your computer through the use of cookies, the use of which is set out below. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browser’s ‘help’ facility.

If you log into our Website using the ‘Connect with Facebook’ button, you are granting permission to Facebook to share your user details with us. This will include your name, email address, country and Facebook profile number.

We use 3rd party organisations to collect non-personally identifiable user information, sometimes through cookies and web beacons. This information allows us to analyse our users’ Website usage as well as the number of visitors, and helps us to improve the site’s services according to our users’ preferences.

**2\. What We Do With Your Information**

Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws.

We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

**3\. Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Website users based on their visit to the Website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

We allow third-party companies to serve ads, including ads based on online behavioural advertising (OAB) and behavioural retargeting practices, and/or to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you, based on your browsing patterns and Website interactions. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

To learn more about this online behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [youronlinechoices.com](http://youronlinechoices.com/), [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

When you opt out of receiving online behavioural advertising, it does not mean that you do not receive advertising when visiting the Website; instead, the advertising you see will no longer be customised.

**4\. Use of Plug-ins**

Some of the Website’s pages use plug-ins provided by other organisations, e.g. the ‘Facebook Like’ or ‘Tweet’ button. These organisations may use information about your visit to our Website on their pages.

If you browse these pages while still being logged into your InsideFutbol.com account, information they collect may be connected to your account on their site. Further information on the use of information by these organisations can be found in their privacy policies.

**5\. Sale of the Business**

If the Business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the Business.

**6\. Updating your details**

If any of the details that you have provided to us change, you can amend these by logging into your InsideFutbol.com account and updating your details by clicking on your username in the top right-hand corner.

If you wish to cancel your registration, please send us an e-mail (address available on our contact page) with your username, name and date of birth. .

**7\. Your Rights**

You have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address and payment of £10 to cover administration expenses.

**8\. Other Websites**

This privacy policy only covers the Website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.

**9\. Consent**

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page and may place notices on other pages of the Website, so that you may be aware of the information that we collect and how we use it at all times. We may also e-mail you should we make any changes so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the services provided by the Website will signify that you agree to any such changes
